Guide to the Leah Salisbury Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Arranged Correspondence and Manuscripts
  - Gibson, William Correspondence: --1958-69-75 --Periodicals --The Cobweb --Cry of Players Amateur/Stock/Off-Broadway --Cry of Players - Berkshire Festiva1 1968 --Cry of Players - Broadway - London l968/69 --Cry of Players - Foreign 1960-70 --Cry of Players - Lincoln Center 1968/69 --Cry of Players - Movie - General --Cry of Players - Movie - M. Poll 1968-71 --Cry of Players - Radio/TV 1958-72 --Cry of Players - Rejections l958-67 --Cry of Players - United Artists 1968 --Dinny & the Witches - Foreign Rights 1960-63 (Box 131)
  - Gibson, William Correspondence: --Golden Boy --John & Abigail --Mass For The Dead 1966-68 --Miracle Worker 1958-64 --Miracle Worker - Amateur & Stock 1959-68 --Miracle Worker - Movie 1959-68 --Miracle Worker - Programs & Publicity 1959-69 --Miracle Worker - Publication 1960-69 --Miracle Worker - Radio/T.V. 1960-67 --Miracle Worker - Recording l962-67 --Miracle Worker - Tahse Tour 1960-62 (Box 132)
  - Gibson, William Correspondence: --Miracle Worker - T.V. version 1956-68 --Miracle Worker - Theatre Guild Tour 1960-61 --Miracle Worker - Foreign 1960-68 --Miracle Worker - Argentina 1960-62 --Miracle Worker - Australia & New Zeland 1960-1962 --Miracle Worker - Brazil 1960-1966 --Miracle Worker - East Africa 1961 --Miracle Worker - England 1960-1963 --Miracle Worker - English Amatuer 1961-1962 --Miracle Worker - France 1959-1966 --Miracle Worker - France (A. Lesser) 1960-1961 --Miracle Worker - Germany 1959-1963 --Miracle Worker - Greece 1959-1961 --Miracle Worker - Holland 1959-1961 --Miracle Worker - Israel 1959-1965 --Miracle Worker - Italy 1959-1968 (Box 133)
  - Gibson, William Correspondence: --Miracle Worker - Japan 1961-69 --Miracle Worker - Mejdco 1960-61 --Miracle Worker - Poland 1962-63 --Miracle Worker - Puerto Rico 1962 --Miracle Worker - Scandinavia l959-62 --Miracle Worker - South Africa 1959-62 --Miracle Worker - Smith America 1959-61 --Miracle Worker - Spain, Portugal 1960-65 --Miracle Worker - Turkey 1961-64 --Poetry 1960-63 --Two For The See Saw - Log Movie 1958-63 --Two For The See Saw - Programs & Publicity --Two For The See Saw - Publication --Two For The See Saw - Radio/T.V./Records --Two For The See Saw - StockAmateur 1959-64 (Box 134)
  - Gibson, William Correspondence: --Two For The See Saw -Tours --Two For The See Saw - Foreign 1958-68 --Two For The See Saw - Australia 1958-62 --Two For The See Saw - Benelux --Two For The See Saw - Brazil 1959-68 --Two For The See Saw - England 1958-63 --Two For The See Saw - France --Two For The See Saw - Germany 1958-59 --Two For The See Saw - Greece 1958 --Two For The See Saw - Hungary 1962-64 --Two For The See Saw - Israel 1959-69 --Two For The See Saw - Italy 1958-66 --Two For The See Saw - Japan l958-66 --Two For The See Saw - Mexico 1958-59 --Two For The See Saw - Poland 1960-61 --Two For The See Saw - Puerto Rico 1959 --Two For The See Saw - Scandinavia 1958-67 --Two For The See Saw - South Africa 1958-63 --Two For The See Saw - Spain & Portugal 1958 -61 --Two For The See Saw - Yugoslavia 1958-1966 (Box 135)
  - Gibson, William Mss. & Printed Copies (Box 136)
  - Gibson, William Mss. & Printed Copies: --A Cry of Players (Box 137)
  - Gibson, William Mss. & Printed Copies: --The Miracle Worker (Box 138)
  - Gibson, William Mss. & Printed Copies: --Two For The See Saw (Box 139)
  - Gibson, William Programs, Reviews, Photos, etc. (Box 140-142)
  - Gibson, William Royalty Statements (Box 143-144)
  - Gielgud, John & Terence Rattigan (Box 145)
  - Gierasch, Stefan (Box 145)
  - Gilden, Bert B. & Katya (Box 145)
  - Gilmore, Edward (Box 145)
  - Gillis, James P (Box 145)
  - Gilner, Elias (Box 145)
  - Gipe, George A. (Box 145)
  - Gillelson, Natalie (Box 145)
  - Giraudoux, Jean Pierre (Box 145)
  - Giunta, Aldo (Box 145)
  - Glass, Fverett (Box 145)
  - Glasser, Ten & Jean Lippmann Block (Box 145)
  - Glaze, Andrew L. (Box 145)
  - Goetz, Ruth Goodman & Augustus 0. Correspondence (Box 146-147)
  - Goetz, Ruth Goodman & Augustus O. Correspondence: The Heiress (Box 148-151)
  - Goetz, Ruth Goodman & Augustus O. Manuscripts (Box 152)
  - Goetz, Ruth Goodman & Augustus 0. Programs, Reviews, Photos, etc. (Box 153)
  - Goetz, Ruth Goodn & Augustus 0.. Royalty Statements (Box 154-155)
  - Goetz, Walter (Box 156)
  - Gold, Michael (Box 156)
  - Goldberg, Herman D. (Box 156)
  - Goldberg, Joe (Box 156)
  - Golden, Joseph (Box 156)
  - Golding, Max (Box 156)
  - Golding Samuel R. (Box 156)
  - Goldman, Harold & Mildred Harris (Box 156)
  - Goldman, James (Box 156)
  - Goldman, Leo (Box 156)
  - Goldsmith, Martin M. (Box 156)
  - Goode, Gerald (Box 156)
  - Goodkind, Howard L. & Norman Garbo (Box 156)
  - Goodman, Jules Eckert & Henry Fisk Carleton (Box 156)
  - Gould, Joan C. (Box 156)
  - Gow, Ronald (Box 157)
  - Goyette, Ronald E. (Box 158)
  - Grady, James (Box 158)
  - Graham, Ronny (Box 158)
  - Grahame, Margot (Box 158)
  - Granowski, Dorian (Box 158)
  - Grant, Micki (Box 158)
  - Gray, Phyllis (Box 158)
  - Gray, Richard & Loiseau, Mayo (Box 158)
  - Gray, Virginia (Box 158)
  - Grayson, Philip (Box 158)
  - Grebanier, Bernard (Box 158)
  - Green, Carolyn (Box 158)
  - Green, Howard J. (Box 158)
  - Greenberg, Edward (Box 158)
  - Greenberg, Michael Alan (Box 158)
  - Greenwood, Omerod (Box 158)
  - Gregory, Andre (Box 158)
  - Gregory, Frank (Box 158)
  - Gregory, Marvin G. (Box 158)
  - Grieve, Rachel (Box 158)
  - Gronowicz, Antoni (Box 158)
  - Gropper, Milton Herbert (Box 159)
  - Grosbard, Ulu (Box 159)
  - Gross, Laurence (Box 160)
  - Gross, Seymour (Box 160)
  - Gross, Stephen (Box 160)
  - Gruber, Edwin (Box 160)
  - Gruskin, Sipora & Edward (Box 160)
  - Guerin, P. (Box 160)
  - Guiles, Fred Lawrence (Box 160)
  - Guilford, Jack (Box 160)
  - Gurney, Hal C. (Box 160)
  - Gwaltney, Doris A. (Box 160)
  - Hackett, Albert & Frances Goodrich Correspondence (Box 161-163)
  - Hackett, Albert R. & Frances Goodrich Correspondence: --Diary of Arms Frank (Box 164-168)
  - Hackett, Albert & Frances Goodrich Manuscripts (Box 169-170)
  - Hackett, Albert & Frances Goodrich Manuscripts - Diary of Anne Frank (Box 171)
  - Hackett, Albert & Frances Goodrich Programs, Reviews, Photos. etc. (Box 172-173)
  - Hackett, Albert & Frances Goodrich Royalty Statements (Box 174)
  - Hackett, Albert & Frances Goodrich Royalty Statements: --Diary of Anne Frank (Box 175)
  - Hamilton, Donald Correspondence (Box 176-179)
  - Hamilton, Donald Manuscripts (Box 180-186)
  - Hamilton, Donald Photographs Printed Works (trans.) Publicity Royalty Statements (Box 187)
  - Hamilton, Donald Printed Works (from magazines) (Box 188)
  - Hamilton, Henry (Box 189)
  - Hamilton, Wallace (Box 189)
  - Hammil, Joel (Box 189)
  - Hammond, Robert M. (Box 189)
  - Handel, Harry L. (Box 189)
  - Handler, Meyer (Box 189)
  - Hanff, Helene M. (Box 189)
  - Hanley, Wi1liam (Box 189)
  - Hannen, Nicholas (Box 189)
  - Harburg, E. Y. & Fred Saidy (Box 189)
  - Haring, Forrest C. (Box 189)
  - Harris, Jed (Box 189)
  - Harris, Lee (Box 189)
  - Harrison, Joel L. (Box 189)
  - Harrison, Samuel B. (Box 189)
  - Harron, Donald (Box 189)
  - Hart, Anita (Box 190)
  - Hart, Jonathan (Box 190)
  - Hartung, Robert (Box 190)
  - Harwood, Geoffrey (Box 190)
  - Haskell, Jack (Box 190)
  - Hastings, Hugh (Box 190)
  - Haubold, Cleve E. (Box 190)
  - Hawthorne, Ruth (Box 190)
  - Hayes, Iola Lynn (Box 190)
  - Hays, Jack (Box 190)
  - Hecht, Rose (Box 190)
  - Heller, John & Martin Stone (Box 190)
  - Heller, Robert (Box 190)
  - Helm, Carl (Box 190)
  - Hemingway, Ernest (Box 190)
  - Hempel, Jeanne (Box 190)
  - Henderson, Lavaniel L., Sr. (Box 190)
  - Herbert, R. Charles (Box 190)
  - Hershey, Lenore 0. (Box 190)
  - Herzel, Roger W. (Box 190)
  - Hethmon, Robert H. (Box 190)
  - Heyward, Dorothy Hartzell Kuhns (Box 190)
  - Hickman, Charles (Box 190)
  - Higley, Philo Correspondence (Box 191)
  - Higley, Philo H. Mss., Contracts, etc. (Box 192)
  - Hill, H. Arnold (Box 192)
  - Hill, Prince (Box 192)
  - Hinsdale, Harriet (Box 192)
  - Hirshfield, Betty (Box 192)
  - Hobbs, J. Kline (Box 192)
  - Hobbs, Peter A. (Box 192)
  - Hochwalder, Fritz (Box 192)
  - Hodder-Williams, Christopher (Box 192)
  - Haetis, Thermistocles (Box 192)
  - Hoffman, Louis (Box 192)
  - Hoffman, Richard Lee (Box 192)
  - Hogan, Frank (Box 192)
  - Hollywood - Nov. 1962 (Box 192)
  - Holm, John Cecil Correspondence (Box 193 & 194)
  - Holm, John Cecil Correspondence & Royalty Statements (Box 195)
  - Holm, John Cecil Manuscripts & Reviews, Programs, etc. (Box 196)
  - Holmes, Ralph D. (Box 197)
  - Horner, Hugh (Box 197)
  - Houlihan, Tom, Jr. (Box 197)
  - Hourwich, George Kennan (Box 197)
  - Howard, Bart (Box 197)
  - Howard, David (Box 197)
  - Howells, William Dean (Box 197)
  - Hubbard, Haven (Box 197)
  - Hubbard, James A. (Box 197)
  - Huchting, Fritz (Box 197)
  - Huffman, Dorothy (Box 197)
  - Hufham, Billy Gary (Box 197)
  - Hughes, Elizabeth Wilson (Box 197)
  - Hughes, Langston (Box 197)
  - Huizinga, Leonhard (Box 197)
  - Hulme, George (Box 197)
  - Hummert, Paul A. (Box 197)
  - Hunt, Florence Vance (Box 197)
  - Hunter, Paul (Box 197)
  - Hunter, Philip (Box 197)
  - Hurst, Mont (Box 197)
  - Hurwit, Lawrence S. (Box 197)
  - Hutchinson, John J. (Box 198)
  - Hutton, Michael Clayton (Box 198)
  - Hynd, Alan (Box 198)
  - Ilma, Viola (Box 198)
  - Incorvia, Victor (Box 198)
  - Ingham, Robert E. (Box 198)
  - Ingram, Jay (Box 198)
  - Ionesco, Eugene Correspondence (Box 199)
  - Ionesco, Eugene Correspondence & manuscripts (Box 200)
  - Isaacs, Edith (Box 201)
  - Isaacs, Charles (Box 201)
  - Ishag, Wares (Box 201)
  - Ives, Helen (Box 201)
  - Jackson, Nagle (Box 201)
  - James, Eric (Box 201)
  - James, Mary Patterson (Box 201)
  - Javor, Frank A. (Box 201)
  - Jay, Verne & Helen (Box 201)
  - Jeans, Ronald (Box 201)
  - Jelenko, Edmond (Box 201)
  - Jenkins, Harry (Box 201)
  - Jenkins, William A.A. (Box 201)
  - Johann, Zita (Box 201)
  - Johnson, J. (Box 201)
  - Johnson, Philip (Box 201)
  - Johnston, Agnes Christine (Box 201)
  - Joseph, Aiston S. (Box 201)
  - Joseph, Richard (Box 201)
  - Joyce, Vincent (Box 201)
  - Kafka, Hans (Box 201)
  - Kaghan, Leonora (Box 201)
  - Kahn, Jesse (Box 201)
  - Kaiser, Joachim (Box 201)
  - Kalett, James M. (Box 201)
  - Kalus, Hy (Box 201)
  - Kamarck, Lawrence (Box 201)
  - Kamins, James (Box 201)
  - Kapelner, Alan (Box 201)
  - Kapner, Stanley H. (Box 201)
  - Karchmer, Andrea (Box 201)
  - Karchmer, Sylvan (Box 201)
  - Kass, Carole (Box 201)
  - Kauffmann, Stanley (Box 201)
  - Kavinoky, Bernice (Box 201)
  - Kazan, Chris (Box 201)
  - Kazan, Elia (Box 201)
  - Kean, Gerald (Box 202)
  - Keefe, Willard Correspondence & Contracts (Box 202)
  - Keffe, Willard Mss., etc. (Box 202)
  - Keenan, Terrance (Box 202)
  - Kellogg, Virginia (Box 202)
  - Kelly, W.C. (Box 202)
  - Kelman, Kenneth (Box 202)
  - Kelso, Edmond E. (Box 202)
  - Kennedy, Harold J. (Box 202)
  - Kenner, James (Box 202)
  - Kenney, Kathryn (Box 202)
  - Kerman, Bernice J. (Box 202)
  - Kerr, Berrilla (Box 202)
  - Kilroy, Thomas (Box 203)
  - Kimmins, Anthony (Box 203)
  - King, Rufus Correspondence (Box 203)
  - King, Rufus Mss. (Box 203)
  - Kirkpatrick, John Alexander (Box 203)
  - Kishon, Ephraim (Box 204)
  - Kleb, William E. (Box 204)
  - Kline, Norman (Box 204)
  - Klussnan, Henry Alexander (Box 204)
  - Kober, Arthur (Box 204)
  - Kobrynsky, Lazare (Box 204)
  - Koenig, Laird (Box 204)
  - Koesis, Robert (Box 204)
  - Kohn, Rose Simon (Box 204)
  - Korman, Seymour (Box 204)
  - Koven, Stanley (Box 204)
  - Kraft, Charlotte (Box 204)
  - Kraft, Hy (Box 204)
  - Kramer, Herman H. (Box 204)
  - Krann, Joseph Correspondence (Box 205 & 206)
  - Kramm, Joseph Manuscripts (Box 207)
  - Kramm, Joseph Programs, Reviews, etc. & Royalty Statements (Box 208)
  - Krantz, Judy Tarcher & Steve Krantz (Box 209)
  - Krass, E. .Stillman (Box 209)
  - Kuner, Mildred Christophe (Box 209)
  - Kurnitz, Harry (Box 209)
  - Kurtz, Maurice (Box 209)
  - LaBar, Tom (Box 209)
  - Labrenz, Theodore (Box 209)
  - Lackner, Stephen (Box 209)
  - Lambert, Reita & Zelda Sears (Box 209)
  - Lamda, Peter (Box 209)
  - Lamson, David (1) (Box 210)
  - Lamson, David (2) - Lamson, Ruth R. (1) (Box 211)
  - Lamson, Ruth Rankin (2) (Box 212)
  - Lan, David (Box 213)
  - Landau, Julius (Box 213)
  - Landis, Jessie Royce (Box 213)
  - Lane, Robert M. (Box 213)
  - Laney, Al (Box 213)
  - Langley, Noel (Box 213)
  - Lanzl, Frank (Box 213)
  - Larralde, Elsa (Box 213)
  - Larson, Victor (Box 213)
  - Latimore, Frank (Box 213)
  - Lauren, Sam & Gladys Lehman (Box 214)
  - Laurence, Lynne (Box 215)
  - Lavery, Emmet G. (Box 215)
  - Lawford, Ernest (Box 215)
  - Lawler, Margretta Scott (Box 215)
  - Lawrence, Annette (Box 215)
  - Lawrence, Jerome (Box 215)
  - Lazarus, Milton (Box 216)
  - Leaver, Phillip (Box 217)
  - Lecture Bureaus (Box 217)
  - Lee, Laurie (Box 217)
  - Lee, Leonard (Box 217)
  - Lee, Robert Charles (Box 217)
  - Leeds, Barbara (Box 217)
  - Leigh, Sylvia (Box 217)
  - Leigh, W. Colston, Inc. (Box 217)
  - Leight, Andrew (Box 217)
  - Lemay, Harding (Box 217)
  - Lengyel, Melchior (Box 217)
  - Lenz, Elinor (Box 217)
  - Leo, Carl (Box 217)
  - Leonard, Jonathan Norton (Box 218 & 219)
  - Lesau, David (Box 220)
  - Leslie, Aleen (Box 220)
  - Leslie, Jean (Box 220)
  - Lester, Elliott (Box 220)
  - Lester, Noel (Box 220)
  - Lettunich, Mateo (Box 220)
  - Levenstein, Alan P. (Box 220)
  - Levinson, Saul (Box 220)
  - Levitan, Cy (Box 220)
  - Levoy, Myron (Box 220)
  - Lewenthal, Raymond (Box 221)
  - Lewenthal, Reeves (Box 221)
  - Lewis, Philip C. (Box 221)
  - Lewis, Shari (Box 221)
  - Ley-Piscator, Maria (Box 221)
  - Liggatt, Lames (Box 221)
  - Lindsley, Fanshawe (Box 221)
  - Lisler, Lauries, Productions Ltd. (Joyce Grenfell) (Box 221)
  - Locke, Sam (Box 221)
  - Lokvam, Marian (Box 221)
  - Lornax, Alton Christie (Box 221)
  - Long, George W. (Box 221)
  - Looker, Patricia (Box 221)
  - Lotito, Louis A. (Box 221)
  - Louis, Toki (Box 221)
  - Love, Elizabeth (Box 221)
  - Lowther, George (Box 221)
  - Ludlum, Edward (Box 221)
  - Lundberg, Clinton (Box 221)
  - Lutyens, David (Box 221)
  - Lynn, Sidney (Box 221)
  - McCann, John (Box 221)
  - McCarthy, Tom (Box 221)
  - McCartney, Russell (Box 221)
  - McCotter, John (Box 221)
  - McCretton, Michael J. (Box 221)
  - McDonald, Frank (Box 221)
  - McDonald, John F. (Box 221)
  - MacDougal, Roger (Box 222)
  - The MacDowell Colony (Box 223)
  - McGuire, Ken (Box 223)
  - Machlis, Joseph (Box 223)
  - McKenna, Norman C. (Box 223)
  - McKinney, Jean Webster (Box 223)
  - MacLane, Barton (Box 223)
  - McLauchlin, Russell (Box 223)
  - MacMahon, Horace (Box 223)
  - MacOwan, Michael (Box 223)
  - McQuaide, Makel (Box 223)
  - Madden, Mark (Box 223)
  - Madison, Martha & Eva Kay Flint (Box 224 & 225)
  - Mallard, Anne (Box 226)
  - Malleson, Miles (Box 227)
  - Malvasso, Michael T. (Box 227)
  - Mamoulian, Rouken (Box 227)
  - Manchester, Joe (Box 227)
  - Manderino, Ned (Box 227)
  - Mandel, Oscar (Box 227)
  - Manley, Ruth R.K. (Box 227)
  - Mann, Peggy (Box 227)
  - Manners, David J. (Box 227)
  - Manns, Robert (Box 227)
  - Mantho, Robert S. (Box 227)
  - Marcus, Harold B. (Box 227)
  - Marcuse, Theodore (Box 227)
  - Maren, Lew (Box 227)
  - Maricle, Leona (Box 227)
  - Marion, Ira (Box 227)
  - Marks, Duke (Box 227)
  - Marlowe, Joan (Box 227)
  - Marsh, Michael (Box 227)
  - Marshall, Constance B. (Box 227)
  - Martin, Charles (Box 227)
  - Marx, Arthur (Box 227)
  - Marx, Sam (Box 227)
  - Massie, Diane Redfield (Box 228)
  - Masur, Harold Q. (Box 228)
  - Mata, Francisco (Box 228)
  - Materials Destroyed (Box 228)
  - Maugh, Peter (Box 228)
  - Maugham, Robin (Box 228)
  - Max, Jerome (Box 228)
  - May, Elaine (Box 228)
  - May, Frederick (Box 228)
  - Mayer, Edwin Justin (Box 228)
  - Mayo, Maria (Box 228)
  - Medcraft, Russell G. (Box 229)
  - Meehan, John (Box 229)
  - Meeker, Ralph & Bob Condor (Box 229)
  - Meiser, Edith (Box 229)
  - Melville, Alan (Box 229)
  - Mercer, William (Box 229)
  - Merrill, Gary (Box 229)
  - Meskill, Robert & Stuart Warrington (Box 229)
  - Metcoff, Jill (Box 229)
  - Michel, Rimsa (Box 230)
  - Michel, Scott (Box 230)
  - Miller, James T. (Box 230)
  - Miller, Joyce (Box 230)
  - Miller, Luby (Box 230)
  - Miller, Peter H. (Box 230)
  - Miller, Roberta (Box 230)
  - Miller, Sigmund (Box 230)
  - Miller, Teresa Lynn (Box 230)
  - Miller, Lucille B. (Box 230)
  - Milton, David Scott (Box 230)
  - Minsler, Jack (Box 230)
  - Minter, Doris Koenig (Box 230)
  - Mintzer, Joseph H. (Box 230)
  - Miskell, Jack Thomas (Box 230)
  - Montross, Lynn (Box 230)
  - Moore, Nancy (Box 230)
  - Morehouse, Ward (Box 231)
  - Morley, Christopher (Box 232)
  - Morley, Robert (Box 232)
  - Merrill, Katherine (Box 232)
  - Morrison, R.L. (Box 232)
  - Morrison, Thomas (Box 232)
  - Morse, Jack (Box 232)
  - Mortimer, David (Box 232)
  - Morton, Frederic (Box 232)
  - Motion Picture Companies (Box 233)
  - Mowbray, Alan (Box 234)
  - Mroz, Charles (Box 234)
  - Mueenuddin, G. (Box 234)
  - Mundy, Dean (Box 234)
  - Murphy, Arthur L. (Box 234)
  - Murphy, Stuart (Box 234)
  - Murray, Robert (Box 234)
  - Musicals (Box 234)
  - Musselman, Morris N. (Box 234)
  - Myerberg, Michael & Joel Spector (Box 234)
  - Nash, Ogden & Hugh Martin (Box 234)
  - Nabutas, Jonas V. (Box 234)
  - Needleman, Rae (Box 234)
  - The New Dramatists Committee, Inc. (Box 234)
  - Newman, Edward (Box 234)
  - Newman, Nathan (Box 234)
  - Newmeyer, Edward F. (Box 234)
  - Nicola, Jon (Box 234)
  - Niles, John Jacob & Rena L. (Box 235)
  - Noah, Robert (Box 236)
  - Noonan, John Ford (Box 236)
  - Noonan, Peggy (Box 236)
  - Nordli, Stephanie Ruth (Box 236)
  - Norris, Sara Lord (Box 236)
  - Mutt, Robert Chelius (Box 236)
  - O'Brien, Bill T. (Box 236)
  - O'Brien, Jack (Box 236)
  - O'Brien, Muriel Ward (Box 236)
  - O'Connell, Hugh (Box 236)
  - O'Connor, William Van (Box 236)
  - Oddo, Jasper (Box 236)
  - O'Donnell, Edwin P. (Box 236)
  - Oelbaum, Jack K. (Box 236)
  - Oestricher, Anne (Box 236)
  - Oglesby, Carl (Box 236)
  - O'Hare. John M. (Box 236)
  - Oliansky, Joel (Box 236)
  - Orkow, Ben (Box 236)
  - Orlovitz, Gil (Box 236)
  - Osborn, David D. & Charles R. Sinclair (Box 236)
  - O'Toole, John (Box 236)
  - O'Toole, William (Box 236)
  - Owen, Paul (Box 236)
  - Pack, Ruth (Box 236)
  - Packard, William (Box 236)
  - Pagano, Jo (Box 236)
  - Page, Tom (Box 236)
  - Pakit, Frank (Box 236)
  - Pally, Erwin (Box 236)
  - Palmer, George (Box 236)
  - Papell, Stan (Box 236)
  - Parish, James (Box 237)
  - Paritz, Jack (Box 238)
  - Parke, James H. (Box 238)
  - Parker, Austin (Box 238)
  - Parker, David (Box 238)
  - Parker, Dorothy (1) (Box 239)
  - Parker, Dorothy (2) (Box 240)
  - Parker, Dorothy (3) (Box 241)
  - Parkhurst, Helen (Box 241)
  - Parsons, Walter H. (Box 241)
  - Pasch, Robert (Box 241)
  - Patton, Jeanette T. (Box 241)
  - Pearce, Alan (Box 241)
  - Peck, Richard E. (Box 241)
  - Peeples, Edwin A. (Box 241)
  - Pepper, Benjamin (Box 241)
  - Perelman, S.J. Correspondence (Box 242)
  - Perelman, S.J. Correspondence: --One Touch of Venus (Box 243 & 244)
  - Perelman, S.J. Manuscripts Photographs Reviews, Clippings, Programs Royalty Statements (Box 245)
  - Perls, Ann [Mary Hiedecker] (Box 246)
  - Perry, Dick (Box 246)
  - Perutz, Kathrin (Box 246)
  - Peters, Paul [James P. Tanner] (Box 246)
  - Petersen, Don (Box 247)
  - Petersen. O.B. (Box 248)
  - Petrova, Olga (Box 248)
  - Pierce, Noel (Box 248)
  - Pierson, Louise Randall (Box 248)
  - Pilcher, Joseph (Box 248)
  - Pinchot, Ann & Ben (Box 248)
  - Pincus, Andrew L. (Box 248)
  - Pinter, Harold (Box 248)
  - Pirandello, Luigi (Box 248)
  - Pirosh, Robert (Box 248)
  - Pittman, Arthur (Box 248)
  - Plaza, Jose (Box 248)
  - Pole, Joseph (Box 248)
  - Pollock, Robert Mason (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box 248)
  - Polsky, Abe (Box 248)
  - Pool, Rosey E. (Box 248)
  - Popplewell, Jack [Richard Russell] (Box 248)
  - Porter, Dorathe H. (Box 248)
  - Porterfield, Robert (Box 248)
  - Portrait, Fvelyn (Box 248)
  - Potts, Ralph Bushnell (Box 248)
  - Poverman, Helen (Box 248)
  - Powell, James F. (Box 248)
  - Powell, Theodore (Box 248)
  - Pratt, Theodore (Box 249)
  - Presnell, Robert R. (Box 249)
  - Presson, Jay (Box 249)
  - Prince, Leslie (Box 249)
  - Pritchard, Barry (Box 249)
  - Producers (Box 249)
  - Producers - Jones, Marrro (Box 249)
  - Producers - Cantor, Arthur (Box 249)
  - Producers - Prince, Harold Company (Box 249)
  - Producers - Arnold Saint-Subber Barefoot in the Park (Box 250)
  - Producers - Stromberg, Hunt (Box 250)
  - Production Costs (Box 250)
  - Prospects (Box 250)
  - Prumbs, Lucille S. Correspondence (Box 251)
  - Prumbs, Lucille S. Manuscripts (Box 252)
  - Psacharopoulos, Nikos (Box 253)
  - Publication Deals and Information (Box 253)
  - Publicity (Box 253)
  - Purcell, Irene N. (Box 253)
  - Raciti, James J. (Box 253)
  - Radbill, Adele (Box 253)
  - Radio & Television (Box 253)
  - Raiden, Edward (Box 253)
  - Random, Darrell (Box 253)
  - Raphaelson, Samson (Box 254-257)
  - Raskin, Eugene (Box 258)
  - Ratcliff, John Drury (Box 258)
  - Rath, Frederick (Box 258)
  - Rathbun, Frank F. (Box 258)
  - Raucher, Herman (Box 258)
  - Raynond, Allen (Box 258)
  - Records - Information (Box 258)
  - Rector, Margaret Hayden (Box 258)
  - Reed, Jesse (Box 258)
  - Reed, Mickey (Box 258)
  - Reed, Tom (Box 258)
  - Reeds, Frank Anton (Box 258)
  - Reich, Richard (Box 258)
  - Rein, Harold (Box 258)
  - Reis, Hilda (Box 258)
  - Reiss, Malcolm (Box 258)
  - Renthal, Sidney (Box 258)
  - Reviews - London Theaters & others (Box 258)
  - Reyher, Ferdinand (Box 258)
  - Reyher, Rebecca Hourwich (Box 258)
  - Reynolds, Wendell S. (Box 258)
  - Rhodes, Marjorie (Box 258)
  - Riaz, Mueno (Box 259)
  - Rice, Elmer (Box 259)
  - Richardson, Donald.M. (Box 259)
  - Richardson, Howard (Box 259)
  - Richardson, Jack C. (Box 259)
  - Riley, Jean (Box 259)
  - Riley, Lawrence Correspondence (Box 260-262)
  - Riley, Lawrence Mansucripts; Reviews; Clippings; Royalty Statements (Box 263)
  - Rill, Eli (Box 264)
  - Road Tour Infonnation (Box 264)
  - Robinson, David V. (Box 264)
  - Rockas, Leo (Box 264)
  - Rodell, John Simon (Box 264)
  - Rodell, Marie F. (Box 264)
  - Rodewald, Josita (Box 264)
  - Rogers, Bill (Box 264)
  - Rogers, Dorothy (Box 264)
  - Rogers, Merrill (Box 264)
  - Rondelle, Roslyn (Box 264)
  - Rosenberg, Henriette (Box 264)
  - Roosevelt, Elliott (Box 264)
  - Roosevelt, Patricia Peabody (Mrs. Elliott) (Box 264)
  - Root, Lynn & Harry Clark (Box 265)
  - Roper, Carol (Box 265)
  - Rose, Dick (Box 265)
  - Rose Ralph & Stephen Longstreet (Box 265)
  - Rose, Stuart (Box 265)
  - Rosen, Isidore (Box 265)
  - Rosen, Leo (Box 265)
  - Rosenau, Anita H. (Box 265)
  - Rosenbaum, Ben (Box 265)
  - Rosenberg, Marvin (Box 265)
  - Rosenfield, Joe, Jr. (Box 265)
  - Rosenstein, Jaik (Box 265)
  - Rosenthal, Saul (Box 265)
  - Rosner, Paul & Richardson, Claike (Box 265)
  - Ross, Arthur A. (Box 265)
  - Rossett, Alan (Box 265)
  - Rossi, Heddy E. (Box 265)
  - Rosten, Norman (Box 265)
  - Roussel, Peter (Box 265)
  - Rouverol, Aurania (Box 266 & 267)
  - Rowe, Virginia (Box 268)
  - Royalties (Box 268)
  - Ruben, Aaron & William Friedberg (Box 268)
  - Ruben, Jose (Box 268)
  - Rubens, Lipora (Box 268)
  - Rubin, Daniel L. (Box 268)
  - Rubin, Edward Rush (Box 268)
  - Rudd, Enid (1) Royalty Statements (Box 268)
  - Rudd, Enid (2) (Box 269)
  - Rude. J. L. & Elizabeth (Box 270)
  - Russian Writers (Box 270)
  - Rutherfurd, Thomas M. (Box 270)
  - Rutledge, Nancy (Box 270)
  - Ryan, Larry (Box 270)
  - Sackler, Howard (Box 270)
  - St. Pierre, Paul (Box 270)
  - Saks, Sol (Box 270)
  - Salaries (Box 270)